// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the biggest technology company in South Korea?",
    answer: "Samsung",
    options: [
      "Oppo",
      "LG",
      "Samsung",
      "Xiaomi"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What was the first soft drink in space?",
    answer: "Coca Cola",
    options: [
      "Coca Cola",
      "Thumps Up",
      "Fanta",
      "Slice"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which country invented ice cream?",
    answer: "China",
    options: [
      "Canada",
      "US",
      "India",
      "China"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Dump,floater and wipe are terms used in which team sort?",
    answer: "Volleyball",
    options: [
      "Cricket",
      "Volleyball",
      "Football",
      "Tennis"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How many points did michael Jordan scores on his first NBA game?",
    answer: "16 Points",
    options: [
      "16 points",
      "20 points",
      "18 points",
      "15 points"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What country has the most natural lakes?",
    answer: "Canada",
    options: [
      "America",
      "Canada",
      "Australia",
      "Paris"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which is the only edible food that never goes bad?",
    answer: "Honey",
    options: [
      "Ice Cream",
      "Milk",
      "Sugar",
      "Honey"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What famous US festival hosted over 350,000 fans in 1969?",
    answer: "Woodstalk",
    options: [
      "Notting Hill Carnival",
      "Robin Hood Festival ",
      "Woodstalk",
      "Diwali"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "FIFA is the global regulatory body of which sports ?",
    answer: "Football",
    options: [
      "Tennis",
      "Football ",
      "Cricket",
      "Hockey"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who was the first indian woman who get an Olympic Medal?",
    answer: "Football",
    options: [
      "P.T.Usha",
      "Sania Mirza ",
      "Aarti Saha",
      "Karnam Malleswari"
    ]
  },
];
